already houses welcome back and in this video I want to talk to you about
已经欢迎回来了 视频我想和你谈谈
strokes now what the heck is a struct in Python well a struct is a way that you
现在，他们是一个结构体 Python 很好结构是你的一种方式
can actually take any type of data in python whether it's numbers letter
实际上可以采用任何类型的数据 python是否是数字字母
strings whatever and you can convert it to bytes format so first question is why
串起来，你可以转换它 到字节格式所以第一个 问题是为什么
would we ever want to do this I mean it might be interesting to know how your
我们是否愿意 这样做 我的意思是 了解你的情况可能会很有趣
computer stores memory or how it transfers data over the network but you really don't care about those ones zeros
计算机存储内存或如何 通过网络传输数据，但 你 真的不关心那些 零
most of the time so why are we learning this well I'm actually going to be
大部分时间都是为什么我们要学习 这个我真的会成为
making a new tutorial series about some network applications in Python and whenever you work with network
关于一些新的教程系列 Python 和 Linux中的 网络应用程序 无论何时使用网络
applications you actually need to read the bytes value so you're on a network
您 实际需要阅读的 应用程序 字节值，所以你在网络上
and you see all these one zeroes coming across and you need to actually interpret it because humans can't read
而且你看到所有这些 零都来了 跨越，你需要实际 解释它，因为人类无法阅读
ones and zeros so we need to figure out a way to take all of that data that raw
为零，所以我们需要弄清楚 一种 获取原始数据的方法
data and turn it into something that's readable for humans so that's why I'm
数据并将其变成某种东西 对人类可读， 这就是为什么 我
going to be showing you how to use strux basically to turn ones and zeros into
将向您 展示如何使用strux 基本上把零和零变成
something that humans can read so the first thing that you need to do is go
人类可以阅读的东西 你需要做的第一件事就是去
from struct imports all and I'll show you guys how to pack and unpack and what
从struct import all ，我将展示 你们这些 如何打包和打包以及 什么
all that means so the first thing I'm going to do is just we're going to have
所有这意味着 ，所以我的第一件事 要做的就是我们 要做的
some data and I'll just have like three numbers like 6 whatever 19 and some float and we'll store his bytes so store
一些数据，我只有三个 无论19还是一些，数字都像6 浮动，我们将存储他的字节存储
as bytes data and someone is texting me actually that's male and it was an
作为字节数据，有人正在 给我发短信 实际上那是男性 而且是一个
update for my Facebook page all right so how do we take data in actually convert
更新我的 Facebook页面没事 如此 我们如何在实际转换中获取数据
it to bytes why would we want to do this well say we're preparing to send some
它到字节为什么我们要这样做 好吧，我们准备送一些
data across the network well let's go ahead and make a variable and I'll just
跨网络的数据以及我们走吧 提前做一个变量 我会 做的
name it pack that up and what you need to do is you need to call a function
把它命名为up up 和你需要的东西 要做的是你需要调用一个函数
called a pack now as you can see before I hit enter this is going to take two
所谓一包 ，现在 你 可以 看到之前 我点击进入这将需要两个
parameters the first one is the format and the second one is going to be a list
参数第一个是格式 第二个将 是一个列表
of values and it can either be just one value like a number or
价值观，它可以只是一个 价值就像数字或
or it can be you know a list like you know ten different numbers
或者你可以知道像你这样的清单 知道十个不同的数字
so remember format and values alright so if you go to the Python documentation
所以记得格式和值 这么好吗 如果你去 Python 文档
they'll say that what you store and they'll give you the the letter for what
他们会说你存储和存储的东西 他们会给你一封什么的信
it is but say that we wanted to distort two integers and a float some decimal
但是说 我们想 扭曲 两个整数 和一个小数点浮点数
point well the key letter for integers is I so
点 那么整数的关键字就是我
if we wanted to store two of them just type I twice and then I'm also going to
如果我们想存储两个人只是 我打字两次，然后我也要去
store a decimal point or float so I'm just going to write that now if I just wanted to store five integers then I'll
存储一个小数点 或浮点数，所以我 如果我只是，那就去写吧 我希望存储五个整数
just write I five times but let's go ahead and start two integers in a float
只写我五次， 但 我们走了 提前并 在浮点数中 开始两个整数
so now with the comma separated this we just need to give it two integers in
所以现在用 逗号 分隔这个我们 只需要给它两个整数
flow so I'll say like six oh 19 and float like four point seven three
因此，我会说像六个 19和19 漂浮得像四点七三
whatever and of course if you're using like strings or characters or anything like that then this is going to be
什么，当然，如果你正在使用 像字符串或字符或任何东西 像那么这将是
different but basically whenever you have data such as this and you want to
不同但基本上每当 你 有像这样的数据，你想
convert it to a byte format just write what type of data you're storing and
将其转换为字节格式只需写入 你正在 存储什么类型的数据
then the data itself simple enough now if you actually just want to see this
那么数据本身就足够简单了 如果你真的只是 想看到这个
right now we can print it out and remember whenever I print this out is
现在我们可以打印出来了 记得每当我打印出来的时候
going to print it out in byte format so this B right here
打算以字节格式打印出来 这个B就在这里
it signifies bytes and now you see all of that stuff so /xo 6 /x double-o all
它表示字节，现在你看到所有 那些东西 所以/ xo 6 / x double-o all
of that crap so again whenever you transfer data over the network that's what's actually being sent so that's why
那个垃圾，所以每当你 在这 网络上传输数据 实际发送的是什么，这就是原因
when a lot of people try to build like password sniffers and they start see you
当很多人 试图建立像 密码嗅探器，他们开始 看到你
know that they're like what the heck so now we know what's going on behind the scenes now I want to show you guys some
知道他们就像那样 现在我们知道背后发生了什么 现在我想向你们展示一些场景
other cool things before I show you guys how to take that byte data and actually
在我向你们展示之前，其他很酷的事情 如何获取该字节数据实际上
convert it back it's a huge human readable form so this is going to come
将它转换回来它是一个巨大的人类 可读的形式，所以这将会到来
in handy later whenever we're learning about why we need to get a certain
每当 我们学习 时，都会派上用场 为什么我们需要得到一定的
amount of bytes so check this out this calc size
字节 数 ，所以检查这个 计算尺寸
this is Bo and function that tells you how many bytes are needed to
这是博功能 告诉你有多少字节 需要
store some value so let me just type I right there
存储一些值，所以让我输入 I 在那里
and let me just type something like f and IIF IIF re so check this out
让我输入 像f 这样的东西 和IIF IIF 重新检查一下
so we're printing out the byte data we already saw that before and now I'm
所以我们打印出 字节数据 我 之前已经看过 了 ，现在我已经看到 了
going to print out the size needed to store an integer a float and our data
要打印出所需的大小 存储一个整数浮点数和我们的数据
which was two integers and a float all right so it says 4 4 12 so whenever
这是两个整数 和一个浮点数 好吧所以它说 4 4 12所以每当
you're sending data across the network and you're sending an integer it takes
您正在通过网络发送数据 你要 发送一个整数
up 4 bytes that's how much space or memory takes up same thing with a flow
最多4个字节，这是 多少空间或 内存在流程中占用同样的东西
very same size 4 bytes each and whenever we try to calculate the size needed to
大小相同， 每个大小4个字节 我们试图计算出所需的大小
store two integers in a float it was 12 and that makes sense 4 plus 4 plus 4
将两个整数存储在浮点数中它是12 这是有道理的4加4 加 4
equals 12 so later on what we're going to be doing
等于12 以后我们要做什么
is we're going to say get the first 12 bytes of this packet or something and
我们要说的是获得前12名 这个数据包的字节或东西
now you guys are like oh so that's why because you know that's how much space
现在你们都喜欢哦所以这就是原因 因为你知道 这是多少空间
it takes up so easy breezy beautiful covergirl already now we need to figure
它占据了如此轻松的微风 covergirl现在我们需要想象
out how to get this data all this byte data and convert it back into human
如何获取所有这个字节的数据 数据并将其转换回人类
readable form well if PAC was the function to make it byte data unpack is
如果PAC是，那么可读的形式 功能使它字节数据解包是
the function to get it back to normal so I'll say to kids I don't know data back
功能让它恢复正常，从而 我会告诉孩子我不知道数据
to normal say to get byte data all right so I'll just name it original data and
正常说来获得字节数据 没事 所以我只是将原始数据命名为
what we need to do is we need to unpack it now whenever you unpack it you also
我们需要 做 的 是，我们需要 解压 它现在每当你打开包装的时候你也是
need to give it the format so it's going to be looking at a bunch of bytes which is actually this thing and it's going to
需要给它格式，所以它会发生 要寻找 一串字节的 这 实际上就是这件事而且它会发生
say ok arm what do you want me to do like are there integers in here are
说 好的胳膊 你想让我做什么 就像这里有整数一样
there characters or there strings are there floats how do you want me to
有 字符或 有字符串 浮在水面上你想要我怎么样
unpack it and we said that there's actually two integers and a float in
打开它，我们说有 实际上有两个整数和一个浮点数
here now is the second parameter you just give it that pack data
这里现在是你的第二个参数 只需给它打包数据
right like that and this is all your bytes that up so now whenever you run
就这样，这就是你的全部 每次运行时都会出现这样的 字节
this and we need to actually print it out then check it out all right so all
这个，我们需要实际 打印它 出则检查出来没事 因此所有
this was from before and now we unpacked it and we got 619 and our float which is
这是从 之前 和现在 我们打开包装 它和我们得到619和我们的浮动
four point seven three and some numbers on the end because computers are awesome
四点七三 和一些数字 最后， 因为电脑很棒
it's storing decimal points but we got a little extra values right there so there
它存储小数点，但我们得到了一个 那里有一些额外的价值
you go so another thing that I'll actually want to show you guys is this if I just copy all of this byte data
你走得那么另一件事 ， 我会 实际上想 告诉 你们这是谁 如果我只是复制所有这些字节数据
right here remember this is basically six nineteen and four point seven three stored as bytes you can actually just do
就在这里记住这基本上是 6个十九岁时 四点七 三 你 可以实际存储为字节
this print unpack iif and put all your byte data right there so this may be a
这个打印打开包装，并把 你 所有 的 字节数据就在那里， 所以这可能 是一个
little bit easier to visually see whenever you first start learning about
有点 容易直观地看到 当你第一次开始学习
this so let me go ahead and run this and we get the same results right there
这样，让我继续这样做吧 我们 在那里 得到 相同的结果
because of course this variable is equal to this right there but basically
因为这个变量当然是平等的 在那里，但 基本上
whenever you have to work with bytes or you need to have byte data and transfer
每当你必须使用字节或 你需要有字节数据和传输
it back into human readable form then you can use pack and unpack from struck
然后它回到人类可读的形式 您可以使用包和解压 来袭
so pretty easy stuff there you go I'll see you guys next
你去的地方非常容易。 我会的 接下来见